[ bright music ]
[ grand music ]
[ dramatic music ]
[ music continues ]
[ bell ringing ]
[ hinge squeaks ]
[ music continues ]
Good morning , Mr. Sullivan .
I have a meeting in a few minutes
with some very jittery stockholders , Mattson .
I hope you have good news for me .
Yes , sir . I do , sir .
Every supermarket tabloid in the country
is running headlines about Andy Barclay and his killer Good Guy doll .
What about his mother and the police that were on the case ?
The police were smart . They denied everything ,
which is fine because now they can 't hurt us .
But the mother 's a different matter .
She backed up her boy 's story in court ,
so now she 's under psychiatric observation .
Jesus . Where 's the boy now ?
Midtown Children 's Crisis Center . Foster custody is pending .
My stomach hurts , Mattson . Is this what you call good news ?
[ stammers ] Yes ... No . I 'm getting to that , sir .
Our biggest problem has been the rumors . A lot ...
[ man ] Good morning , Mr. Sullivan .
A lot of people are saying that some joker here at the company
must have tampered with the doll 's voice cassette , you know ?
" Hi . I 'm Chucky . I 'm the Lakeshore Strangler .
" And now I 'm gonna kill you . " [ chuckles ] Something like ...
Well , something like that .
[ clears throat ] But the good news , Mr. Sullivan ,
is that now we 've got the doll .
[ lock buzzes ]
We 've rebuilt it from head to toe .
A lot of it was burned to a crisp , but everything checks out ,
the voice cassettes , the servomechanisms .
We 've found absolutely nothing .
This is a quality control report .
I 'm sure it will make the stockholders very happy .
I want to see the doll for myself .
Absolutely . [ clears throat ]
[ knocking on door ]
[ over intercom ] Gentlemen , Mr. Sullivan 's here . We ready ?
Well , give us a minute . We 're not used to making them manually .
[ whirring ]
[ tense music ]
[ machine stops ]
[ beeping ]
- What 's wrong ? - I don 't know , it 's stuck .
Just "
They 'll have this worked out .
[ machine whirring ]
[ crackling ]
[ man gasping , chattering ]
[ indistinct shouting ]
Oh , Jesus !
[ man groaning ]
[ screaming ]
[ electricity crackling ]
[ social worker ] Andy , you still dreaming about Chucky ?
Sometimes .
- You want to talk about it ? - No .
Come on , Andy . Remember what I told you ?
Talking helps make
- the nightmares go away . - Nightmares go away .
[ chuckles ]
Well , Chucky was trying to take over my soul .
Why ?
He was this bad man who got inside my Good Guy doll ,
so he wouldn 't have to go to hell .
But then he wanted to get inside me .
Why , Andy ?
' Cause if he stayed inside the doll too long ,
he 'd be trapped in there .
He needed me ' cause I was the first person he told his secret to .
What secret ?
That his real name was Charles Lee Ray .
Boy , that 's a scary dream .
It was .
You know , dreams can 't hurt you .
Dreams aren 't real .
- Right ? - Right .
- [ dramatic music ] - Here .
In there .
[ indistinct radio chatter ]
Let 's hurry up .
Mattson , I don 't care what it takes . Put a lid on this .
Yes , sir . That 's not a problem . I 'll take care of this .
Listen to me .
You smother this or you 're out of here in 24 hours . You got that ?
Yes , sir .
Now , if you will excuse me , I 've got a meeting I 've got to get to .
As far as the stockholders and I are concerned ,
this matter is finished .
Yes , sir .
Uh , what do you want me to do with the doll ?
Stick it up your ass .
[ tense music ]
[ Grace ] Naturally , he was badly traumatized by the murders ,
but they bounce back pretty fast at that age .
Poor kid .
What Andy needs now is a normal family environment , a fresh start
and a chance to forget the past .
Since you two have done so well with so many kids ,
we were hoping you might foster him until his mother recovers .
- There 's always room for one more . - Mm .
What 's that supposed to mean ?
Uh , well ...
He seems normal enough , but how has all this affected him ?
Well , in order to come to terms with
something he couldn 't possibly understand ,
he turned it all into a kind of fairy tale .
He insisted his doll was responsible .
He said it was possessed by the soul of Charles Lee Ray .
[ Phil ] Who ?
The Lakeshore Strangler .
He murdered a dozen people in this series of ritual voodoo killings .
Are we even qualified to take care of a boy like this ?
Well , I understand your concern , Mr. Simpson ,
but I 'm sure you can see that this is just a child 's way
of coping with a difficult situation .
Andy 's fine now .
He just wants to get on with his life .
So , Andy , what do you like to eat ?
All kinds of things .
Well , what 's your very favorite food in the whole wide world ?
Chocolate .
[ both laugh ]
Besides chocolate .
Mm . My mom used to fix me eggs for breakfast . I like eggs .
You got it . We should stop at the store .
- [ Phil ] Uh , the one down here ? - [ Joanne ] Yeah , the organic ...
[ Phil ] You 're in luck , Andy . Joanne 's a terrific cook .
You like sushi ? You know what I mean by ...
Phil , look out !
- Jesus Christ ! - [ screeching ]
[ horn blaring ]
[ dramatic music ]
[ kids chattering ]
[ boy 1 ] Look out for the car .
[ boy 2 ] Hey , wait up .
[ sighs ]
Make yourself comfortable , Andy .
Thanks .
[ Phil ] Well , I have to get back to the office this afternoon .
[ Joanne ] I thought that you 'd done everything .
[ Phil continues talking indistinctly ]
[ clock ticking ]
[ Phil ] Ah-ah-ah ...
First rule . Don 't touch the old stuff .
Sorry .
Well , that 's okay . No foul .
It 's just that we collect this junk ,
and a lot of it 's kind of fragile .
- You like it ? - Uh-huh .
It 's been in my family for three generations .
My grandmother gave it to my mother , and my mother gave it to me .
And who are you gonna give it to ?
Why don 't you take this upstairs and explore ?
I 'll be up there in a minute .
Okay .
- What do you think ? - [ chuckles ]
Oh , I 'll get used to him .
[ chuckles ]
[ muffled pop music playing ]
[ exhales ]
Jesus . Did you ever hear of knocking ?
[ Joanne ] Andy , did you find ...
What ? Are you crazy ? Give them to me .
Come on , Joanne .
Phil will shoot you if he catches you again .
Andy , this is Kyle . She 's staying with us , too .
Charmed .
Kyle , what is this ?
You 've been here three weeks . Why haven 't you unpacked ?
[ scoffs ] What for ?
I 've never spent more than a month in any home .
[ Joanne ] With that attitude , I can see why .
Come on . Put these things away ,
and then would you do me a favor and help me get dinner started ?
[ Kyle ] Can 't . Got to work tonight .
Kyle , that 's the third night in a row .
I 'd really like it if you 'd spend a little time with the family .
I need the money . I 'm gonna be on my own next year .
Yes , well , until then , you 're with us , okay ?
- Come along , Andy . - [ Andy ] Bye .
[ Joanne ] I think you 'll be very happy here .
This is your room , right here .
I made those curtains just for you .
I bet blue is your favorite color .
Take a look around . I 'll start to unpack .
Wow !
I thought you might like those . Um ... There 's more in the closet .
Before dinner , we 'll go explore the backyard .
And , later , I 'll read you some stories .
Would you like that ?
There are lots of kids your age in the neighborhood , Andy .
I 'm sure you 're gonna make all sorts of new friends .
- [ dramatic music ] - [ Andy yells ]
Hey , hey , hey !
Andy , rule number two , no running in the house .
It 's only a doll . Andy , are you listening to me ?
Oh , Andy , I 'm so sorry . I didn 't realize that was in there .
We 've had so many kids here , it 's hard to keep track of everything .
I 'll get rid of it .
Hi , I 'm Tommy . And I 'm your friend till the end .
Why don 't we get settled in , and then we 'll have some dinner , okay ?
[ honking ]
Shit .
[ alarm activator beeps ]
[ Mattson grunts ]
[ Mattson groans ]
[ engine starting ]
[ dialing ]
Hello , Gabriella . Guess who ?
[ laughs ]
That 's right .
The vodka ? Oh , the vodka .
Of course I remembered the vodka .
Two-week anniversary . You think I 'd forget the vodka ?
I know what that does to you .
Okay , well , wait for me .
On my way . Yeah .
Shit .
[ tense music ]
[ alarm chirps ]
[ thunder rumbling ]
[ phone rings ]
I want to play Red Light .
No , Sammy , I don 't want to play Red Light now .
I want you to go back to bed right now .
[ Sammy ] But I 'm scared .
There 's nothing to be scared of . It 's just a storm .
Grace Poole .
[ Chucky ] Yes , I 'm trying to reach Andy Barclay .
[ Grace ] Andy no longer lives here . Who is this ?
This is his Uncle Charles .
Sorry , cash only .
But that 's a gold card . That 's just as good as cash .
Not here , it ain 't . We don 't accept credit cards .
I don 't carry cash , okay ?
[ horn honking ]
- [ car alarm blaring ] - Oh ...
[ alarm continues blaring ]
[ alarm stops ]
[ engine starting ]
[ Chucky ] Don 't move !
Jesus !
God . Okay . Okay , what do you want ?
- No questions . Just drive . - Okay , okay .
[ thunder crashing ]
[ tense music ]
[ Chucky ] Keep going .
[ thunder rumbling ]
[ Chucky ] Now , park this piece of shit .
Put your arms behind the seat .
- [ Mattson ] What ? - [ Chucky ] Do it !
Okay . Take it easy . Take it easy . Please , don 't , don 't shoot .
Look , I ... I don 't carry cash . I got ... I got a gold card .
I 'll give you anything you want . Tell me what you want .
Freeze , asshole .
[ Mattson ] Take my ... Take the car .
And you can drop me off , but just , please , leave me alone .
[ sobs ] Please .
Bang . You 're dead .
[ whimpers ]
[ laughs maniacally ]
[ Mattson laughs nervously ]
[ muffled groaning ]
[ laughs maniacally ]
[ engine revving ]
[ Mattson muffled ] No ! No ! No !
- [ continues laughing ] - [ Mattson ] No ! No ! No !
- [ Chucky continues laughing ] - [ Mattson groaning ]
[ thunder rumbling ]
[ tense music ]
" The woodcutter argued for a long time with his wife ,
but she was such a horrid , frightening woman when she was angry ,
that in the end he agreed to her plan .
In the morning , their stepmother called them .
' I think it would be nice if we all went into the forest today , ' she said .
Hansel and Gretel did not reply ,
but followed their parents into the dark forest . "
Where they all lived happily ever after .
- No , they don 't . - Well , they do for now .
We 'll finish it tomorrow night , okay ?
Don 't go .
What 's the matter ?
I miss my mother .
Oh , honey , I know you do .
Will I ever see her again ?
Of course you will . I promise .
Don 't worry . I 'll stay with you as long as you want .
[ Andy ] My mother used to sing to me . Will you sing to me ?
[ Joanne clears throat ]
[ Joanne hums softly ]
[ tense music ]
[ thunder rumbling ]
[ Joanne continues humming ]
Shit .
Hi . I 'm Tommy .
Shut up , you idiot .
I like to be hugged . I like to be hugged .
- I like to be hugged . - Hug this .
I like to be hugged . I like to be hugged . I like ...
- What was that ? - Nothing . Now go to sleep .
Nobody 's going to hurt you .
[ thunder rumbling ]
- [ dramatic music ] - [ figurine shatters ]
[ laughs ]
[ continues laughing maniacally ]
Eat dirt , Tommy .
[ laughing maniacally ]
Do either of you have anything to say about this ?
I think we should talk to a lawyer first .
Kyle , that 's not funny . That statue was very important to me .
I think one of you owes Joanne an apology .
I 'm innocent .
Andy ?
I didn 't do it .
All right . You leave me no choice .
Until somebody fesses up , you 're both grounded .
[ Kyle ] But I have a date tonight .
Sorry .
This is exactly how I wanted to spend my day off . Thanks a lot .
But I didn 't break the statue . Really .
Yeah . Maybe it just fell , huh ?
Hey . You want to hear me say your name backwards ?
Kyle .
[ chuckles softly ]
Hold this .
[ coughs ]
Jesus . Give me that .
What the hell do you think you 're doing ?
I wanted to taste it .
Get real . It tastes like shit , okay ?
These things are very bad for you .
Then why do you do it ?
Because grown-ups are allowed to do things that are bad for them .
You 're not a grown-up .
[ sighs ]
You 're beginning to get on my nerves , Andy .
Now , why don 't you give me a hand over here ?
Mr. Simpson is kind of grouchy , isn 't he ?
He 's not so bad .
I 've had fosters that would shoot you
for staring at them cross-eyed .
Really ?
Sure .
They figure you 're not theirs . You 're just passing through .
The minute you screw up ...
Argh ! They let you have it .
You know , I got to tell you , I 'm not happy with this whole thing .
Having second thoughts ?
Well , you have to admit , he 's a very troubled little boy ,
and he obviously has not come to terms with this whole doll thing .
[ exhales ]
Look , all I 'm saying is that he may need
more attention than we can give him .
Phil , Andy 's been through hell .
You have to give him some time . He 'll settle down .
Besides , I like him .
I hate you .
Hi . I 'm ... Tommy , and I 'm your friend to the end .
Hidey-ho . [ laughs ]
[ tense music ]
Hi .
- Hi . - Hi .
Kyle , do you miss your mom and dad ?
You can 't miss someone you never knew .
Where are they ?
I have no idea .
My dad left before I was born .
My mom put me up for adoption when I was three .
Do you remember her ?
I made it a point to forget .
It 's easier that way .
Hey . Break time .
Move over .
Want a push ?
No , thank you .
Come on . It 's fun .
Come on , Andy , please , I just want to sit here , okay ?
[ Andy ] Too late . There you go .
[ Kyle ] Andy , come on . Give me a break . Stop it .
[ Andy laughs ] No .
[ tense music ]
- [ Kyle ] Andy , I 'll kill you . - [ Andy laughs ]
[ Kyle ] Come on . Let me off !
Andy .
I 'll get you .
- Come on , Andy , cut it out . - Dinner !
- Come and get it . - [ Andy ] Whoa .
Aah !
Mayhem . Come on . I 'll race you .
[ Andy ] No fair . You got a head start .
[ Kyle ] Excuses , excuses . Don 't forget your doll .
[ tense music ]
[ music continues ]
For Kyle . Think she 'll like it ?
[ scoffs ] What do I know about teenage girls ?
More than you did three weeks ago .
I 'm not so sure .
I was thinking we should get something for Andy .
Make him feel more settled . Any ideas ?
Yeah . How about a Valium ?
[ tense music ]
[ muffled yelling ]
[ Chucky ] Surprise .
Did you miss me , Andy ? I sure missed you .
- [ muffled yelling ] - [ Chucky ] I told you .
We were gonna be friends to the end .
And now it 's time to play .
I got a new game , sport .
It 's called Hide the Soul .
And guess what ? You 're it .
[ muffled yelling ]
[ chanting in foreign language ]
Give me the power , I beg ...
[ branches rustling ]
This isn 't over , you little shit .
I 'm not gonna spend the rest of my life as a plastic freak .
Next time you 're alone , you 're mine .
[ window slides open ]
[ muffled yelling ]
Oh , my God .
It 's Chucky . Look out !
- Shut up . You 'll wake Phil and Joanne . - Kill him ! Kill him !
Andy , stop it , will you ?
What the hell is this , now ?
It 's Chucky . I told you he 'd find me . He tried to take over my soul .
Andy , calm down .
You didn 't have to wait up .
Yeah ? You know , Kyle , I don 't believe you .
You actually tied this child up , so he wouldn 't tell on you .
- Is that it ? - Oh , come on , Phil .
- Chucky did it ! - That 's enough now .
Chucky ? I ... I 've had it .
[ Andy ] But you 've got to kill him .
[ Joanne ] Andy !
Please , listen to me . I 'm not lying .
If you don 't kill him , he 'll come get me .
Andy , calm down .
I 'm going to get rid of it .
There , see ? He 's gone . He can 't bother you anymore .
- [ tense music ] - [ door shuts ]
No .
I 'm turning human again ?
If I don 't get out of this body soon , I 'm screwed .
Come on , Andy . We 're late .
Andy . Don 't forget your lunch .
Egg salad .
Mmm , yum !
Now , whatever you do , don 't act nervous , okay ?
They 'll smell a new kid a mile off . Just act like you belong .
What are you looking for ?
Nothing .
Is it Chucky coming to get you ?
[ children chattering ]
Andy , how did you manage to tie yourself up like that last night ?
I already told you .
Get real .
You 're just like everybody else . You don 't believe me either .
- [ boy ] Kyle . - Hey , Autumn .
[ Autumn ] Hi .
Why 'd you have to leave so early last night ? You missed all the fun .
Story of my life .
[ kids chattering indistinctly ]
[ tense music ]
- [ kids chattering ] - [ blows whistle ]
[ Chucky ] Come on now .
Where is it ?
[ tense music ]
Ah-ha !
" Pinocchio jumped for joy , shouting , ' I 'm alive ! I 'm alive ! '
Then the talking cricket said ... " What 'd he say ?
" ' If you 're very , very good , and promise to tell no lies ,
then you will become a real , live boy . '
Boys who are bent on following their caprices
and will have their own way , sooner or later repent . "
Get lost , microchip .
Am I boring you , Andy ?
[ Andy ] No , Miss ... Kettlewell .
[ Andy ] Kettlewell .
I have precious little patience for disruptive students .
But he just whacked ...
Especially new students , whose utmost concern
should be getting on my good side .
[ bell rings ]
[ Miss Kettlewell ] I want those desks spick and span before anyone leaves .
[ objects clattering ]
[ kids chattering ]
[ tense music ]
[ gasps ]
Andy ! You think this is funny ?
- I didn 't do that . - [ bell rings ]
Go ahead , kids . Don 't forget the spelling test tomorrow .
Not you . Come over here . Sit down and get comfy .
You 're going to be here for a while .
But I didn 't do it , I swear .
No ? Then who did ?
Don 't even think about it .
No toys . Head down .
Head down .
[ ominous music ]
- [ Chucky ] Peekaboo ! - [ Andy gasps ]
[ Chucky ] Please , let me out of here , Andy .
It 's dark in here .
[ Andy grunting ]
I promise I won 't kill anyone else . Okay ?
Now , open the goddamn door !
[ Andy grunting ]
Let me out , you little dick !
Let me the fuck out !
[ tense music ]
[ doorknob rattling ]
Andy , I told you to stay in your seat . Come out of there .
Open this door right now .
Andy , come out this very second .
Andy ! Andy !
[ tense music ]
Andy ?
Andy , this isn 't funny .
[ gasps ]
[ tense music ]
- [ Chucky yells ] - [ groans ]
[ screams ]
You 've been very naughty , Miss Kettlewell .
[ music continues ]
[ fingertips squeaking ]
[ screaming ]
Andy , what 's this all about ?
Chucky followed me to school . He tried to get me again , so I ran home .
Do you know what 's he talking about ?
His teacher called ,
said she was keeping him after school for detention ,
said he wrote an obscenity on his paper .
Chucky did it .
All right , Andy . Come on .
This is going to stop ,
' cause I will not allow this foolishness in my house .
Do you understand ? Open the door .
- [ Joanne ] Oh , Phil . - Joanne , please .
Open the door .
Open it .
Open it !
Now , I want you to look down there and tell me what you see .
[ tense music ]
It 's Chucky , but ... His name is Tommy ,
and he 's been there since last night , hasn 't he ?
Hasn 't he ?
For crying out loud , Joanne , the child needs professional help .
Oh , stop pretending you 're worried about Andy .
You never wanted him here in the first place .
[ Phil ] That 's not true .
[ Joanne ] So , what are you suggesting we do ? Send him back ?
[ Phil ] You don 't have to make it sound so horrible .
[ Joanne ] Do you have any idea how traumatic that would be ?
[ Phil ] Traum ... For whom , Joanne , for him or for you ?
Look , if that kid stays here , he 's gonna tear this family apart .
[ Joanne ] Family ? Is this what you call a family ?
Families don 't just give up on their children .
[ Phil ] Joanne , he 's not our child .
[ door slams shut ]
It 's not the end of the world .
But they 're gonna send me away .
[ Kyle sighs ]
You 'll be okay .
Where will I go ?
Andy .
I 've lived with dozens of different families ,
and they always seem to send me away
just when I 'm getting comfortable ,
- but you know what ? - What ?
Every time it happens , it just makes me stronger ,
because it reminds me that the only one I can count on is myself .
Okay ? And you have to learn that now .
I know it sounds tough ,
but you 'll deal with it .
It doesn 't matter .
Wherever I go , Chucky will find me .
[ tense music ]
[ whirring ]
[ music continues ]
[ board creaks ]
- [ loud creaking ] ' [ gasps ]
- [ creaking ] ' [ gasps ]
[ clattering ]
[ electric knife whirs ]
[ ominous music ]
[ buzzes ]
[ knife whirs ]
[ knife whirring ]
[ footsteps pattering ]
[ gasps ]
[ music continues ]
[ Chucky yells ]
[ dramatic music ]
[ grunting ]
[ whirring ]
[ Chucky continues yelling ]
[ announcer on TV ] advances over the declines
by a seven to six margin .
Decent [ indistinct ] today , with the ...
[ TV clicks off ]
What 's wrong ?
I thought I heard something downstairs .
It 's one of the children .
That 's what I 'm afraid of .
- [ dramatic music ] - [ both grunting ]
[ knife whirring ]
Why fight it , Andy ? We 're gonna be very close .
In fact , we 're gonna be fucking inseparable .
[ both grunting ]
[ Chucky yells ]
What the hell 's going on down ... [ gasps ]
Andy ...
Put down the knife .
But I need it for ...
Just put the knife down , and we 'll talk about it .
[ knife powers down ]
[ ominous music ]
Everything is gonna be just fine .
[ yelling ]
[ groaning ]
How 's it hanging , Phil ?
[ Phil grunting ]
[ Phil screaming ]
[ bones snap ]
No . Oh , God . Phil . Phil .
I 'll call an ambulance .
Phil . Phil .
Oh , God ! No !
Oh , God ! Oh !
Get away from me !
Oh , God !
[ Joanne sobs ]
[ indistinct radio chatter ]
[ indistinct chattering ]
[ man ] No , we didn 't hear anything . Nothing .
[ indistinct radio chatter ]
I should have listened to him .
He 'd have been here now if only I 'd listened to him .
It 's not your fault .
I 'll take care of this .
Andy , you 'll be fine now .
You 'll come stay at the center with us for a few days
until we can find you a new family .
We 've placed Kyle with a number of families .
Things always seem to work out okay .
Don 't they ?
Yeah .
There 's your stuff .
Come on , Andy . Let 's go .
He 's still in the cellar , Kyle . Don 't let him get you , too .
[ Grace ] Andy ?
We 'll be out of your way in just a minute here .
Did anyone , besides the boy , witness the accident ?
- Okay .
Let 's go .
[ tense music ]
[ ominous music ]
[ gasps ]
[ breathing sharply ]
[ thudding ]
Joanne !
[ music continues ]
[ sewing machine whirring ]
[ sewing machine continues whirring ]
[ sewing machine whirring faster ]
Joanne ?
Joanne !
[ Chucky yells ]
[ dramatic music ]
[ both grunting ]
[ gasps ]
[ tense music ]
[ Kyle yelps ]
Bitch . You hurt me .
How much further till we get to the kid ?
A ways .
Step on it .
What 's the rush ?
If I don 't get out of this body soon , I 'll be trapped in here !
What are you looking at ?
[ engine starting ]
[ siren wailing ]
Floor it .
Get real . This is a station wagon .
Shit !
Pull over .
[ indistinct radio chatter ]
Behave yourself .
I 'll kill you if I have to .
Okay , honey , let 's see your license .
You were clocking 60 in a 45 . What 's your hurry ?
I have a date .
You 're gonna have to do better than that .
That 's one of those Good Guys , isn 't it ?
Yes , it is .
I love these things . What 's your name , buddy ?
- Chucky . - [ laughs ]
That 's incredible .
I 'll say .
What the hell 's that ?
[ ominous music ]
You 've seen dolls that pee ?
This one bleeds . [ chuckles ]
[ indistinct radio chatter ]
Okay , look ,
just slow it down , huh ?
And buckle up for safety .
[ engine starting ]
Now , get going .
[ indistinct radio chatter ]
You okay , honey ?
Mmm-hmm .
- Don 't let the bedbugs bite . - [ chuckles ]
Come on . Step on it .
Fine . We 'll just get pulled over again .
Just shut up and drive before I kick your fucking teeth in .
[ tense music ]
[ brakes screeching ]
[ Chucky yelling ]
- [ yelling ] ' [ gasps ]
You goddamn women drivers !
[ dramatic music ]
[ yelling ]
Fuck .
Fucking bastard .
Shit . Andy .
[ tense music ]
- [ gasps ] - Playtime 's over .
[ fire alarm ringing ]
[ kids exclaiming ]
[ indistinct chattering ]
[ alarm continues ringing ]
[ tense music ]
Andy , what are you doing ?
Come on . We 've got to get out of the building .
Kyle , what 's going on here ?
You did this , didn 't you ?
He did it .
Get into my office .
Is this your idea of a joke ?
Oh , just give me that .
Amazing , isn 't it ?
[ Grace gasps , screams ]
[ dramatic music ]
[ screaming ]
Come on !
[ banging on door ]
Okay , sport , we 're gonna have a little game of Chucky Says .
Chucky says , " Move your ass . "
Snap out of it !
You act like you never seen a dead body before !
[ sirens wailing ]
Andy , come on ! Open it .
Andy ! Open the door !
- [ woman ] Come on ! Everybody out ! - [ sirens blaring ]
[ horns blaring ]
[ dramatic music ]
[ indistinct radio chatter ]
Inside . Hurry .
[ tense music ]
Stop !
- Come on . - [ engine sputtering ]
Come on .
[ engine starting ]
[ tires squealing ]
[ fireman ] Hey , lady , slow down , will you ?
[ music continues ]
♪ Passin ' by ♪
[ tires squealing ]
Say your prayers , Andy .
[ horn honking ]
God damn it !
[ honking ]
[ music continues ]
[ continues honking ]
♪ I first saw you ♪
- [ honking ] - Pull over !
- What ? - [ Kyle ] Pull over !
Pull over !
[ tense music ]
Hey ! Just what in the hell do you think you 're doing ?
Let me go . Let me go .
[ driver ] What the fuck 's wrong with you ?
Let go !
Crazy bitch !
[ dramatic music ]
[ tense music ]
We 're home .
[ Andy groans ]
Close your eyes and count to seven .
When you wake , you 'll be in heaven .
[ laughs maniacally ]
This is it , world .
From now on , no more Mr. Good Guy .
[ chanting in foreign language ]
Give me the power , I beg of you .
[ dramatic music ]
[ thunder crashing ]
[ Chucky chanting in foreign language ]
[ chanting growing louder ]
[ storm stops ]
[ ominous music ]
No ! [ echoing ]
[ tense music ]
You little shit !
Do you know what you 've done ?
It 's too late ! I 've spent too much time in this body .
I 'm fucking trapped in here !
[ box thuds ]
What the hell ?
Andy , run .
[ dramatic music ]
[ yelling ]
- Andy . - Kyle !
Are you okay ? Come on .
[ music continues ]
[ Kyle ] Shit !
- [ groans ] - Andy ! Hurry up !
Let 's go . I 'll go first . Stay right behind me .
[ tense music ]
Come on .
Andy , step on it .
Reach ! Give me your hand !
- Andy ! - [ shouts ]
[ Kyle ] Stop yourself . Grab the side .
[ yells ]
Andy ! Hurry up ! He 's right behind you .
[ Chucky ] Little bastard !
[ dramatic music ]
Don 't look back . Come on . Hurry !
- [ Chucky ] You can 't get away from me ! - Give me your hand !
- Reach ! - [ Andy grunting ]
[ Andy ] I 'm gonna kill you , Andy !
[ screaming ]
Come on . Go ! Go ! Go ! Run down there .
I 'm gonna get you fuckers !
[ music continues ]
[ grunts ]
[ grunting ]
God !
[ screaming ]
Oh , God !
[ groans ]
[ music continues ]
[ gasps ]
Come on . Do it !
[ grunting ]
Come on . Give me your hand .
Don 't be afraid . Come on .
Closer . Closer so you can grab my hand .
Andy . Now !
[ Chucky screaming ]
[ Kyle grunts ] Can 't open it .
How will we get out ?
We 'll have to find another way . Give me your hand .
I hate kids .
[ tense music ]
[ machine malfunctioning ]
[ alarm sounding ]
Terrific .
[ tense music ]
[ machine whirring ]
[ yelps ]
[ Andy gasps ]
[ sizzling ]
[ music continues ]
[ grunts ]
[ Chucky yells ]
[ screams ]
- [ Andy groans ] - [ alarm blaring ]
[ alarm stops ]
[ sizzling ]
- [ clattering ] ' [ gasps ]
[ Chucky laughs ]
- Duck ! - [ Andy gasps ]
[ dramatic music ]
[ screaming ]
Do it !
[ yelling ]
Andy , please .
I was only playing .
[ screaming ] No , please ! Oh , please !
[ dramatic music ]
[ Chucky ] God , it hurts ! [ shouts ]
[ screams ]
No ! No ! God ! No ! No ! No !
[ screaming ]
Holy shit .
We did it .
Let 's get out of here .
[ dramatic music ]
- Let 's see . Are you okay ? - Yeah .
What 's this ?
Thanks for coming after me .
Yeah , well , you owe me one , squirt .
Kyle !
[ shouts ]
[ dramatic music ]
I 've got you now , Andy ,
and you know what I 'm gonna do to you ?
I 'm gonna cut off your legs , too .
[ dramatic music ]
[ Chucky shouts , grunts ]
[ sizzles ]
Huh ?
[ gasps ]
No !
[ screaming ]
Kyle ! Kyle !
Kyle ! Kyle ! Kyle , wake up !
Kyle !
Come on . Come on .
Ugh ! God . What did you do to him ?
All right , Andy .
[ Chucky yells ]
[ Andy and Kyle scream ]
[ dramatic music ]
Kyle ! Kyle !
Eat this , you son of a bitch .
[ Chucky gagging ]
Come on .
[ grand music ]
[ Andy ] Where are we going ?
[ Kyle ] Home .
[ Andy ] Where 's home ?
[ Kyle ] Andy , I have no idea .
[ music continues ]
[ playful , creepy music ]
[ tense music ]
[ dramatic music ]